<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NMSTU Directory</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Multidisciplinary\nCollege of MST\nUniversity\nG.I. Nosova</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">example, address</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_theme">Change theme</string>
    <string name="imageViewCollege">College photos</string>
    <string name="menu_info">Info</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="menu_about">About app</string>
    <string name="menu_short_history">Short history</string>
    <string name="gallery_text">Photos were made by Gazim</string>
    <string name="about_text">Project about college was made by 4 students from «ISPp&#8211;20&#8211;2»:\nSoliev Gazimyan - made this app and added photos\nNikitin Yaroslav - found the information\nFilippova Veronica - gave the idea to make this application and made the introduction\nYashina Vladislava - found the information</string>
    <string name="info_text">"    The Multidisciplinary College (MDC) is a modern educational institution operating in the university complex of the Moscow State Technical University. GI Nosov\". It consisted of three colleges and a technical school: “Magnitogorsk Industrial College named after N.I. Makarov”, “Magnitogorsk State Professional and Pedagogical College”, “Magnitogorsk Construction College” and “Magnitogorsk Trade and Economic College”.\n\n    Today, the college is studying full–time more than 2.6 thousand students in the enlarged groups of specialties:\n\n    &#8211;construction technique and technology;\n    &#8211;informatics and computer technology;\n    &#8211;electric and heat power engineering;\n    &#8211;mechanical engineering;\n    &#8211;applied geology, mining, oil and gas business and geodesy;\n    &#8211;material technology;\n    &#8211;technique and technology of land transport;\n    &#8211;economics and Management;\n    &#8211;service and tourism;\n    &#8211;history and archeology.\n   \n    A multidisciplinary college today is an educational complex, where all conditions have been created for the training of competent specialists.\n\n    The multidisciplinary college is included in the TOP&#8211;500 educational organizations of the Russian Federation implementing secondary vocational education programs, as well as in the TOP&#8211;10 educational organizations of the constituent entity of the Russian Federation based on the results of monitoring the quality of training in 2020.\n\n    The college has a modern material and technical base: laboratories and training and production workshops of the college are equipped with the necessary equipment, stands, teaching and visual aids, as well as teaching and monitoring materials in accordance with the specifics of training sessions. The educational process for receiving education by students with disabilities is carried out in specially equipped premises of the Multidisciplinary College.\n\n    Special attention in the college is paid to the development of the information and educational (electronic) environment (IEEE), which is aimed at the formation of a creative, intellectual and socially developed personality, formed on the basis of a variety of information educational resources, modern information and communication tools and pedagogical technologies.\n\n    The specialists are trained by a creative, efficient teaching staff, which numbers 141 teachers, of which: 77 teachers have the highest qualification category, 16 candidates of science, four teachers are Honorary Workers of Education. More than 16 teachers of the college are acting experts for the demonstration exam, 4 are experts with the right to hold a regional championship held according to WorldSkills standards, 1 expert is a master.One of the most important tasks of the management of the Multidisciplinary College is to provide continuous education in the conditions of the university complex, which is implemented in several directions:\n\n    the formation of a stable interest among MPC students in participating in scientific and creative projects, research conferences, forums, competitions.\n\n    expanding the interaction of teachers of graduating subject&#8211;cycle commissions with specialized departments of the university, meetings of students with leading teachers of departments and famous alumni.\n\n    Every year, decades and weeks of specialties and disciplines are held, within the framework of which there are intracollegiate olympiads, competitions of professional skills, scientific and technical exhibitions, open defenses of term papers and final qualification works in the form of diploma projects, newspaper contests and other events that contribute to the development of creative, scientific and research activities of students.\n\n    Under the guidance of teachers, students of the multidisciplinary college defend the honor of the educational institution at olympiads and competitions of various levels &#8211; from urban to all&#8211;Russian. Among them:\n\n    International Certification Olympiad \"Trajectory of the Future\" (Microsoft, English, Photoshop, 4D modeling) &#8211; 2020 &#8211; 10 people received certificates Microsoft specialist, 2019 reached the final in the Microsoft nomination (Word and Excel &#8211; 1st place)\n\n    All&#8211;Russian competition for popularizers of science \"Science without Borders\" &#8211; diploma, 1st place, 2019All&#8211;Russian sectoral competition of diploma projects of the Association of educational institutions of the metallurgical complex of Russia; nomination Diploma projects in metallurgical specialties &#8211; diploma for the 2nd place; 12.2019\n\n    All&#8211;Russian Olympiad of professional skills of students in the specialty SPO UGS SPO 22.00.00 Technologies of materials &#8211; diploma for the 2nd place, 2019\n\n    All&#8211;Russian competition of creative projects and ideas for the development of social infrastructure \"NEOTERA\", specialty 08.02.01 Construction and operation of buildings and structures &#8211; 1st degree diploma, 2018\n\n    VII open regional championship \"Young professionals\" (WorldSkills Russia) South Urals 2019&#8211;2020 in the competence \"Electrical installation\" &#8211; diploma for the 3rd place, 2019\n\n    VII open regional championship \"Young Professionals\" (WorldSkills Russia) South Ural 2019&#8211;2020 in the competence \"Maintenance and repair of relay protection and automation\" &#8211; diploma for the 2nd place, diploma for professionalism, 2019\n\n    Regional Olympiad of professional skills of students under secondary vocational education programs in educational institutions of the Chelyabinsk region in an enlarged group of specialties 13.00.00 \"Electricity and heat power engineering\" &#8211; diploma for the 1st place, 2020.\n\n    Regional Olympiad of professional skills of students enrolled in secondary vocational education programs in educational institutions of the Chelyabinsk region in the enlarged group of the specialty 22.00.00 \"Technologies of materials\", diploma for the 1st place, 2020\n\n    Ural regional championship in sports programming (qualification round) specialty 09.02.03 Programming in computer systems, 09.02.07 Information systems and programming, 2019\n\n    According to the results of the city Spartakiad among students in training programs for mid&#8211;level specialists in the city of Magnitogorsk in the 2019&#8211;2020 academic year, the teams of college boys and girls became bronze medalists in track and field athletics, the best in volleyball and a chess tournament, in shooting, the women's team took 1st place, and the men's &#8211; 3rd place. According to the results of all sports competitions, the junior team of the Multidisciplinary College took FIRST PLACE, and the women's team became SECOND.\n\n    The college pays special attention to creating a comfortable environment. Work is actively underway to improve the premises of the college and student campus. In 2019, its own public garden appeared on the territory of the MpK.\n\n    In addition to comfortable recreation areas, there is a stele with the logos of the university and the All&#8211;Russian Trade Union of Education, installed in the park in honor of the 100th anniversary of the student trade union movement in Russia.\n\n    In 2020, on the basis of the college, a wide&#8211;profile stadium with an obstacle course of 7,000 square meters was opened, including a jogging track, two football fields, equipped basketball and volleyball courts, horizontal bars and special equipment for physical education.\n\n    The college staff pays much attention to the formation of the socio&#8211;cultural environment: there are more than 15 student associations of various orientations in the college, interaction with the student trade union committee of MSTU, with city youth associations has been established.\n\n    The hallmark of MpK is a quality education, a caring attitude towards students, a strong school of mentoring and class leadership, and a strong connection with social partners."</string>
    <string name="direction_text_15">UGS code Specialty code - Name\n\nDepartment number No. 1 General education\n\n08.00.00 - CONSTRUCTION TECHNIQUES AND TECHNOLOGIES\n08.02.01 - Construction and operation of buildings and structures\n08.02.09 - Installation, adjustment and operation of electrical equipment of industrial and civil buildings\n09.00.00 - INFORMATICS AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING\n09.02.01 - Computer systems and complexes\n09.02.07 - Information systems and programming\n13.00.00 - ELECTRIC - AND HEAT POWER ENGINEERING\n13.02.11 - Technical operation and maintenance of electrical and electromechanical equipment (by branches)\n15.00.00 - ENGINEERING\n15.02.03 - Technical operation of hydraulic machines, hydraulic drives and hydropneumoautomatics\n15.02.12 - Installation, maintenance and repair of industrial equipment (by branches)\n15.02.14 - Equipping with automation of technological processes and production (by industry)\n21.00.00 - APPLIED GEOLOGY, MINING, OIL AND GAS AND GEODESY\n21.02.05 - Land and property relations\n22.00.00 - MATERIALS TECHNOLOGY\n22.02.01 - Metallurgy of ferrous metals\n22.02.05 - Metal Forming\n23.00.00 - ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGIES OF LAND TRANSPORT\n23.02.04 - Technical operation of lifting and transport, construction, road machinery and equipment (by branches)\n23.02.07 - Maintenance and repair of engines, systems and assemblies of cars\n38.00.00 - ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT\n38.02.01 - Economics and Accounting (by branches)\n43.00.00 - SERVICE &amp; TOURISM\n43.02.15 - Cooking and confectionery\n46.00.00 - HISTORY AND ARCHAEOLOGY\n46.02.01 - Documentation Support, Management and Archival Studies\n\nDepartment No. 2 Information Technologies and Transport\n\n09.00.00 - INFORMATICS AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING\n09.02.01 - Computer systems and complexes\n09.02.07 - Information systems and programming\n23.00.00 - ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGIES OF LAND TRANSPORT\n23.02.03 - Maintenance and repair of road transport\n23.02.04 - Technical operation of lifting and transport, construction, road machinery and equipment (by branches)\n23.02.07 - Maintenance and repair of engines, systems and assemblies of cars\n\nDepartment No. 3 Mechanical, Hydraulic Equipment and Metallurgy\n\n15.00.00 - ENGINEERING\n15.02.03 - Technical operation of hydraulic machines, hydraulic drives and hydropneumoautomatics\n15.02.12 - Installation, maintenance and repair of industrial equipment (by branches)\n15.02.14 - Equipping with automation of technological processes and production (by industry)\n22.00.00 - MATERIALS TECHNOLOGY\n22.02.01 - Metallurgy of ferrous metals\n22.02.05 - Metal Forming\n\nDepartment No. 4 Construction, Economics and Service Sector\n\n08.00.00 - CONSTRUCTION TECHNIQUES AND TECHNOLOGIES\n08.02.01 - Construction and operation of buildings and structures\n08.02.09 - Installation, adjustment and operation of electrical equipment of industrial and civil buildings\n13.00.00 - ELECTRIC - AND HEAT POWER ENGINEERING\n13.02.11 - Technical operation and maintenance of electrical and electromechanical equipment (by branches)\n21.00.00 - APPLIED GEOLOGY, MINING, OIL AND GAS AND GEODESY\n21.02.05 - Base Land and property relations\n38.00.00 - ECONOMICS AND MANAGEMENT\n38.02.01 - Economics and Accounting (by branches)\n43.00.00 - SERVICE &amp; TOURISM\n43.02.15 - Cooking and confectionery</string>
    <string name="college_site_link">www.magtu.ru</string>
    <string name="short_history_text">"    The Multidisciplinary College (MDC) is a modern educational institution operating in the university complex of the FSBEI HPE \"MSTU\".\n    \n    As an educational organization, the Multidisciplinary College was createdon the basis of the Government decree of December 22, 2009 No 2039 \"On the reorganization of the state institution of highervocational education \"Magnitogorsk StateTechnical University named after GI. Nosov \". It consisted of three colleges and a technical school: “Magnitogorsk Industrial College named after N.I. Makarov”, “Magnitogorsk State Professional and Pedagogical College”, “Magnitogorsk Construction College” and “Magnitogorsk Trade and Economic College”.\n    \n    Thus, each educational institution, being independent, played a big role in education the city of Magnitogorsk and the training of specialists in secondary links for enterprises, institutions and organizations of the city:\n    \n    -Magnitogorsk Industrial College them. N.I. Makarova was a \"forge of personnel\" for PJSC MMK\n    -Magnitogorsk State vocational pedagogical college trained city specialists\n    -Magnitogorsk Construction College trained specialists forcity construction industry\n    -specialists of the Magnitogorsk trade Economic College worked in enterprises trade and service sector in Magnitogorsk.\n    \n    Thus, having united, this study place has become the best option in the city for preparing students for a specialty."</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
</resources>